

Mohamad M Maninang

WEB/REACT DEVELOPER

SUMMARY

Web developer with 6 years of experience coding and building multiple e-commerce websites.

Proficient with ASP.Net Frameworks, C#,
Javascript, HTML, CSS, JQuery, SQL
Server and upgraded my front end skills by joining ZTM Academy by learning
React.JS, Next.JS, React Native and
Node.JS. Improved the user experience and average time on e-commerce cart pages both for co-developers and clients.

PERSONAL DETAILS

Address

2389 Esmeralda Street, San Andres Bukid Manila, Philippines

CONTACT

- mohammadmaninang94@gmail.com
- 09364777064
- © Enter URL without http://
- in mohammad-maninang-41b7311a5
- mohammadmaninang94

WORK EXPERIENCE

.Net Developer

TIREWEB MARKETING 2016-present

Building ecommerce websites specialising in retailer websites, ecommerce and software for the tire, wheel and automotive industry with C#, Javascript, JQuery, HTML, CSS (SCSS) and .Net Frameworks.

- Improved cart pages and user experience by building a generic script with javascript that can calculate items with services, fees and taxes dynamically for different clients.
- Integrated Payment gateways like Paypal, Square, Apple Pay, Affirm, etc.
- Refactored code or modules than can be more easily maintained and understood in the long run.
- Software Engineer

MEDILINK NETWORK, INC. 2015-2016

Building internal projects for HMO like Maxicare with C#,VB, Javascript, JQuery, HTML, CSS (SCSS) and .Net Frameworks.

React Developer

ZTM ACADEMY 2020-Present

Build an e-commerce app with Redux, Hooks, Stripe, Firebase https://crwn-clothing-live-v1.herokuapp.com/

EDUCATION

React.JS

ZTM ACADEMY 2020-Present

BS in Information Technology

STI COLLEGE 2010-2014

SKILLS

HTML	CSS	JAVASCRIPT	C#	React.JS	JQuery	SCSS	SQL Server	Redux
Redux Thunk		Redux Saga	Firebase	Enter skill				